[{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678868472,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":19142,"timeElapsed":69660},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678874717,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":6244,"timeElapsed":75905},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678892547,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":17829,"timeElapsed":93735},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678898287,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":5740,"timeElapsed":99475},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678904557,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":6268,"timeElapsed":105745},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678907746,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3188,"timeElapsed":108934},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678912082,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":4335,"timeElapsed":113270},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678915503,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3421,"timeElapsed":116691},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678918573,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":3068,"timeElapsed":119761},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678925708,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":6075,"timeElapsed":126896},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678927594,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":1885,"timeElapsed":128782},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678930505,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2911,"timeElapsed":131693},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678933051,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2545,"timeElapsed":134239},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678936846,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":3794,"timeElapsed":138034},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678939728,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":2882,"timeElapsed":140916},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678946586,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":6857,"timeElapsed":147774},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678951546,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":4959,"timeElapsed":152734},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678954932,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":3385,"timeElapsed":156120},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678961910,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":5584,"timeElapsed":163098},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678963984,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":2073,"timeElapsed":165172},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678967123,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":3138,"timeElapsed":168311},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678973694,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6570,"timeElapsed":174882},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678979030,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":5335,"timeElapsed":180218},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678982176,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":3145,"timeElapsed":183364},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678987085,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":4908,"timeElapsed":188272},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678990496,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":3411,"timeElapsed":191684},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678993991,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":3494,"timeElapsed":195179},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678999312,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":5320,"timeElapsed":200500},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679007605,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":7237,"timeElapsed":208793},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679009133,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":1527,"timeElapsed":210321},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679012007,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2873,"timeElapsed":213195},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679015276,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3268,"timeElapsed":216464},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679018421,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3144,"timeElapsed":219609},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679022294,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":3872,"timeElapsed":223482},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679025519,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":3224,"timeElapsed":226707},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679027994,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":2474,"timeElapsed":229182},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679031455,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":3461,"timeElapsed":232643},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679048797,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":16347,"timeElapsed":249985},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679051389,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":2592,"timeElapsed":252577},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679055429,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":4039,"timeElapsed":256617},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679057937,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":2507,"timeElapsed":259125},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679060179,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2241,"timeElapsed":261367},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679063254,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":3074,"timeElapsed":264442},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679067602,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4347,"timeElapsed":268790},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679070310,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2707,"timeElapsed":271498},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679073274,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2963,"timeElapsed":274462},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679080623,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":5961,"timeElapsed":281811},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679082902,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2279,"timeElapsed":284090},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679086191,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3288,"timeElapsed":287379},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679087739,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":1547,"timeElapsed":288927},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679092377,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":4637,"timeElapsed":293565},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679094669,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":2292,"timeElapsed":295857},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679098253,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":3583,"timeElapsed":299441},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679101885,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3631,"timeElapsed":303073},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679107144,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":5259,"timeElapsed":308332},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679111094,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":3949,"timeElapsed":312282},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679116276,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":3985,"timeElapsed":317464},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679117938,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":1662,"timeElapsed":319126},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679122914,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":4975,"timeElapsed":324102},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679124700,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":1786,"timeElapsed":325888},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679128212,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":3511,"timeElapsed":329400},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679130889,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":2677,"timeElapsed":332077},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679136010,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":5120,"timeElapsed":337198},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679138791,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":2780,"timeElapsed":339979},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679141954,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":3163,"timeElapsed":343142},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679154169,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":11061,"timeElapsed":355357},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679155598,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":1428,"timeElapsed":356786},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679157101,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1501,"timeElapsed":358289},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679158549,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":1447,"timeElapsed":359737},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679163172,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":4621,"timeElapsed":364360},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679164477,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":1303,"timeElapsed":365665},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679167588,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":3110,"timeElapsed":368776},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679170157,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":2567,"timeElapsed":371345},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679180011,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":9853,"timeElapsed":381199},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679199053,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":17595,"timeElapsed":400241},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679200663,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":1609,"timeElapsed":401851},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679202120,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":1457,"timeElapsed":403308},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679203662,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1541,"timeElapsed":404850},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679206128,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":2465,"timeElapsed":407316},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679209013,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2884,"timeElapsed":410201},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679213539,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":4525,"timeElapsed":414727},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679216098,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2558,"timeElapsed":417286},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679218821,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":2722,"timeElapsed":420009},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679225785,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":5864,"timeElapsed":426973},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679227470,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":1684,"timeElapsed":428658},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679229201,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":1730,"timeElapsed":430389},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679230692,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":1490,"timeElapsed":431880},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679233461,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2768,"timeElapsed":434649},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679235123,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1660,"timeElapsed":436311},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679239348,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":4224,"timeElapsed":440536},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679241527,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2179,"timeElapsed":442715},{"subjectID":"el0mf6mbvn","prolificID":"62cd43d66c2dd7ae9ab53ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b417e8ccbb8e14423a6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679246913,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":5385,"timeElapsed":448101}]